Kevin Titco

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

An AWS certified candidate who is on track to obtain a networking degree presents with a proven track record of being able to transition into fields with steep learning curves. As part of clinical staff, has slashed overhead costs by 16% and sought drug costs savings upwards of \$32k per year. With 5+ years in healthcare and a diverse work history that comprise of B2C sales, construction, legal, and manufacturing - I seek to leverege my unique work experience in Z Networks.

Experience

08.2018 - present Certified Technician

UW Medicine - Harborview Hospital, Seattle

- · Perform imaging, objective tests, patient query, and triage
- Outperform colleagues by 30% in patient encounter productivity in a month
- Manage smooth clinic flow and collaborate with team with a can-do attitude
- Utilize strong interpersonal skills at every patient encounter
- Self-initiate tasks/projects including digital signs and printed solutions

10.2016 - 04.2019 Certified Technician

Eye Associates Northwest, Seattle

- Spearheaded creation of excel-based tools such as point-based systems used for performance reviews which quantified a technician's skill
- · Performed clinical tests, prior authorization, triage and billing

^{05.2016 - 10.2016} Technician

Northwest Eye Surgeons

Summarized patient chief complaints and performed objective tests

08.2013 - 11.2018 Freelance Web Design

Freelance Developer, Seattle

- Designed and developed website from scratch via Photoshop, HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript
- Increased image upload speed by 10% for improved user experience
- Applied skills in setting goals, time management, and organization with devotion to technology

^{08.2013} - ^{11.2014} IT Staff

Joy of Pilates, Bellingham

JoyofPilates.net

Managed website contents within WordPress via HTML and CSS

Education

04.2019 - present North Seattle College, Seattle

Associates of Applied Science, Network and Server Administration

09.2010 - 06.2014 Western Washington University, Seattle

Bachelor of Science, Kinesiology - Prehealthcare Specialization

Certificates

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

Validation Number X2PPZ402FM1QQPSE



Stay In touch

Email kevintitco@gmail.com

Phone 3602202568

Address Yale Avenue N. Seattle, WA 98109

Citizenship US

Website superherokevin.com

Skills Summary

Adaptability in steep learning curves

Communication and interpersonal skills

Linux

VLSM Subnetting, network toplogy, DNS

VPC and launching EC2 Instances

Windows









Languages

CSS

JavaScript

MySQL

PHP

Python ***